<resources>
    <string name="app_name">lslsfdsfsdfsdfsdfsdfsdfsdfsfdsdfsdfsdfsfdsfdsdfsdfsfd</string>
    <string name="kushal">Traveling is one of the most valuable and enriching experiences in our lives
increasing our knowledge, opening our minds, enriching our spirits, extending new moral
values; and you can find many destinations in the world that would fulfill your desires.
But, if what you are looking for is a unique and memorable experience that will give you
the opportunity to learn about another culture through art, cultural events, historical cites,
and archeological treasures, a place to visit is certainly Italy. Among many places in the
world where you can relive the past, Italy is certainly the most charming place. This little
country in the middle of the Mediterranean represents the cradle of the Roman Empire
and the Renaissance, and offers an incredible number of opportunities for people eager to
learn about an ancient civilization that shaped the history of many cultures. Moreover,
“according to UNESCO” (“United Nations Educational, Scientific and CulturalOrganization”), Italy is the place where you can find 66% of the “world‟s historical
artistic heritage”, which is an incredible number if you consider that Italy is only
“116,346.5 sq mi” (“Art Cities”) (“Italy”). Although every little corner of this country
will be unforgettable to you because all of its towns and cities are “...veritable living
museums” (“Art Cities”), there are two cities that you cannot miss because of their
beauty and their historic, cultural, and artistic value, and these cities are Rome and
Venice.
Rome is a large city in the middle of the Country and historically was the center
of the Roman Empire and of Christianity; today the center of the Catholic Church of the
entire world is in the Vatican City, which although it is considered a separate state, is
located in the center of Rome (“Rome”). Rome is also the capital of Italy and has “two
and a half thousand years”(“Rome”) of history and art in its buildings and museums,
offering cultural visitors the opportunity to learn about architecture, art and many aspects
of western civilization through guided educational tours. Many of the historic sites and
museums can be reached by foot once you have reached down town, and I would suggest
taking a walk, if it is possible, because not only will the famous historical landmarks
amaze you, but also the urban architecture is worth a view. Although there are many
things to see in Rome, some of the most popular sites to visit are the Colosseum, the
Pantheon, the Trevi Fountain, the Forum and the Vatican museum, which includes
Leonardo and Raphael masterpieces and Michelangelo‟s famous fresco: “The Last
Judgment” located in the Sistine Chapel. For all of them you can either plan a personal
visit or arrange a tour with a group. In both cases you will have a guide that will explain
all the features of these wonderful works of the past and their roles in the life of theancient Romans. For instance, did you know that the Colosseum that you see in pictures
of Rome was constructed starting in “72 AD”, and it was there that gladiators fought to
the death (“Colosseum”). This and even more is waiting for you in Rome. Not to mention
that between one visit and another you can always enjoy great Italian food, which is
considered one of the finest cuisine. Moreover, as one of the most visited cities in
Europe, Rome provides tourists with many opportunities to experience cultural events;
many of them are especially made for international visitors to show the customs and
traditions of the region. Often, there are food festivals, traditional music festivals or
parades, depending on the time of the year. A list of events can be easily found on the
Internet or in many information centers around the city, which display useful directories
translated in several languages. To conclude, Rome is the largest city in the Country and,
probably, one of the most attractive cities in the world and its history is beyond anything
people from the USA are used to seeing and experiencing because Roman history dates
back 2000 years. Therefore, Rome is an ideal destination for cultural travels eager to
learn about the ancient culture.
After your tour in Rome, which will leave you tired but very pleased, you can
comfortably rest in a railway car that, in only 4 hours, crossing a beautiful part of the
country will take you to Venice, the most unique city in the world. Venice is an amazing
city in northeast Italy built on more than 100 islands (“Venice”). The palaces, the
innumerable canals with buildings sinking vertically into the water, the numerous artistic
bridges, and the long tradition in family owned craft businesses which produce masks,
laces, and beautiful glass works, make this city a perfect destination for travelers who
wish to enrich their lives with memorable experiences. The center of the city, San Marcosquare, includes the prominent Doge‟s Palace built in the gothic style and the Bridge of
Sighs, where the convicts coming from the Doge‟s palace would walk and say good bye
through the stone bars to wonderful Venice before entering the prison (“Doge‟s Palace”)
(“Bridge of Sighs”). Next to the palace is San Marco‟s Basilica, a great example of
“Byzantine and Gothic architecture” (“St Mark‟s Basilica”). The Basilica is also known
as the “Church of gold” because of its luxurious design and its mosaics covered with
golden dust. Finally attached to the Basilica stands the red tall campanile, symbol of
Venice. Of course, this is not the only place to visit. There are many other churches,
bridges, palaces and museums to see that cannot be easily listed. But what makes this
experience unique is that you will be able to admire some of this beauty comfortably
sitting on a ferry or, maybe, on a gondola enjoying an educational and relaxing tour of the
city. Guides tell interesting stories and legends about the many bridges and narrow canals
that will fulfill your curiosity. Moreover, if you want to learn where glassblowing came
from and the story that brought this wonderful craft to the New World, you must visit
Murano Island, which has a long tradition in glassmaking dating back to 1291 (“Murano,
the Glass Island”). Or maybe your hobby is making beautiful laces; in this case Burano
Island is the place to see where beautiful lace works are displayed, from table linens to
wedding dresses. Finally, during the two weeks before Mardi Gras (around February and
March), Venice turns into a world of bright colors and mystery on the occasion of Venice
Carnival, and if you have the chance to visit the city during this time you will see the
most beautiful and famous Venetian craft masks. As you probably noticed Venice
provides many opportunities to cultural travelers to enrich their lives; learning not onlyabout history, art, and architecture, but also about some local business traditions that had
a significant influence on the past.
In conclusion, I believe that Venice and Rome are without any doubt a perfect
example of what the Italian peninsula can offer because of their historical and artistic
heritage and their unique, romantic, and magical look. Most of the world‟s historical sites
are in Italy, and an incredible number of masterpieces from the Renaissance period, like
Michelangelo‟s and Raphael‟s works, are preserved in Italian museums. Moreover, Italy,
is one of the most popular destinations for cultural tourists; therefore you can find exactly
what you are looking for: educational tours and cultural entertainment. So, if this is what
you have always desired, make your dream come true and live a once-in-a-life experience
in Italy.</string>
</resources>